500affiliates.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy Agreement | +500Affiliates™

## Privacy Policy Agreement

This website is operated by Plus500 ("we, us or our”). It is our policy to respect the confidentiality of information and the privacy of individuals. We are also bound by principles contained in the Data Protection Act 1998. This Privacy Policy Statement outlines how we manage and protect the personal information you give us and hold about our customers and others (“The Policy”). By visiting our website and using our services you agree to this Policy.

This Policy will be reviewed from time to time to take account of changes to our operations or practices and, further, to make sure it remains appropriate to any changes in law, technology and the business environment. Any information held will be governed by our most current Policy.

**What information do we collect?**

You supply us with personal information through the account application form, which we retain. We also maintain information as a result of your trading activity and website usage. When you visit our website or use our services, we may also log your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access device. For quality and control purposes we may monitor and record communications with you. Generally, this information is obtained when you agree to register as a customer and use our services.

**How do we use it?**

We use information about you in the following ways:

  * We use your personal details and information obtained from other sources for the purpose of satisfying regulatory and legal requirements, for marketing, administration and customer services, to analyse your purchasing preferences and to ensure that the content, services and advertising that we offer are tailored to your needs and interests. We keep your information for a reasonable period for these purposes. We may need to share your information with our service providers and agents. Generally, we require that organisations who handle or obtain personal information as service providers acknowledge its confidentiality and undertake to respect an individual’s right to privacy and comply with Data Protection principles including this Policy.
  * We or agents acting on our behalf may:
    * perform identity, money laundering and fraud prevention checks and may pass your details onto other group companies, financial and other organisations (including law enforcement agencies) involved in fraud prevention and detection who may use your information in the same way;
    * investigate your credit standing and in doing so may contact banks, financial institutions and credit reference agencies;
  * We continually enhance the content and function of our website, software and services. For this reason, we monitor customer traffic patterns and website usage to help us improve the design and layout of our website and provide content that is of interest.
  * By providing us with your personal information you consent to our processing your personal data for the above purposes. You also consent to our transferring your information, for the above purposes, to countries or jurisdictions which may not provide the same level of data protection as the UK.

**Use of cookies**

We may use information obtained about you by accessing cookies (text files which are stored by your computer or other access device) when you visit our website or use our services. Cookies store small pieces of information, such as names and email addresses. We do this to allow us to identify users, ensure your information is secure and personalise the website and our services wherever possible. We are able to do this by including web beacons (also known as clear GIFS or web bugs) in our emails. Web beacons do not store additional information on your computer but, by communicating with our cookies on your computer, they can tell us when you have opened emails from us and which pages you look at.

If you wish to delete any cookies that are held on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your computer’s file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. If you want to stop cookies being stored on your computer in future, please refer to your browser manufacturer’s instructions by clicking “Help” in your browser menu. Further information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.AboutCookies.org. Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our website or services.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse a user’s use of the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full website functionality. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

**How do we protect your information?**

161We take appropriate measures to ensure that the information you disclose to us is secure, accurate, up to date and kept only for so long as is necessary for the purposes stated. It is held in secure computer storage facilities and subject to procedures to prevent accidental loss, destruction or damage.

**Other Information**

You should note that if our business (or any part of it) is sold or transferred at any time, the information we hold may form part of the assets transferred although it will only be used in accordance with this Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Policy at any time so you are encouraged to review it from time to time. We will, of course, notify you of any changes where we are required to do so.

You are entitled to ask for a copy of the information we hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to have any inaccuracies in your information corrected. Please notify us of any changes of address or any other personal circumstances to enable us to maintain a correct record.

**When and how to contact us**

If your personal details change, if you have any queries about how we use your information, or wish to help us improve this Policy, please notify us by contacting us at: [support@plus500.com](mailto:support@plus500.com)
